

ENURA INDULA

Assisstant Product Manager cum UI/UX Engineer

CONTACT

Address:

Al Quoz, Dubai, UAE

Phone:

+971582056700

Visa Status:

Visit Visa (From Jan to Apr)

Email:

sri.indula@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/enura-indula/

WWW:

https://enuraindula.github.io/

SKILLS

- Research & Trend Analysis
- Product Management
- Strategic Planning
- Project Management
- Client Communication
- UI & UX Management
- HTML & CSS
- Adobe XD, Figma & Zeplin

ABOUT

Diligent UI/UX Engineer cum Assistant Product Manager offering 4 years of industry success, including product roadmap development, market research, data analysis, UI development, and UX management. Have experience in IT & Education industries. Highly skilled in identifying opportunities to maximize product quality and company revenue. Driven and strategic with a proven history of well-managed UI/UX engagement and product launch prowess.

WORK HISTORY

Assistant Product Manager cum UI Engineer

2021 - 06 2021 - 12

ESOFT Technologies PVT. LTD, Sri Lanka

- Analysing product performance and redesigning as required.
- Designing, developing and managing activities from product definition & planning to production and release.
- Developing the product strategy and roadmap.
- Managing prioritisation and trade-offs between customer experience, business impact, performance, and post-launch support.
- Collaborated with project and product managers to integrate UI features complying with prescribed code standards.
- Working cross-functionally with design and technology teams to ensure timely and quality release of product/ enhancements.

UI/UX Engineer cum Product Strategist

2020 - 04 2021 - 05

TechLead International PVT, LTD, Sri Lanka

- Established criteria for each milestone within the product roadmap as means to measure developmental progress.
- Conceptualized and deployed enhanced product features and optimized implementation for use in marketing strategies.
- Coordinated design meetings and decisions across other internal departments and teams.
- Managed cohesive design quality across more than five projects, adhering to prescribed themes and functional choices.

UI & UX Content Creator

2018 - 01 2020 - 02

Uplabs Inc. Delaware Corporation, USA

- Collaborated with project and product managers to integrate
 UI features complying with prescribed code standards.
- Apply qualitative and quantitative analysis techniques to continually improve the end user experience.
- Developed Application UIs via emerging UI tools such as Adobe XD, Figma & Zeplin.

EDUCATION

Masters of Sciences in Information Systems

Atlantic International University - United States of America

Currently reading fully remotely

Bachelor of Sciences (Honours) in Computer Science

Kingston University - London, United Kingdom

- First Class
- Majored in Software Engineering
- Batch Top Academic Year 2020/21

Pearson BTEC Higher National Diploma in Computing

Esoft Metro Campus - Sri Lanka

- Majored in Software Engineering
- Batch Top Academic Years 2018/20

Pearson International Diploma in Software Engineering

Esoft Metro Campus - Sri Lanka

• Completed with an Overall Distinction.

CERTIFICATIONS & AFFILIATIONS

 Introduction to Software Product Management

University of Alberta

• Project Management Foundations: Teams

Project Management Institute Inc.

Computer Society of Sri Lanka

Affiliated by IEEE

Business Analysis: Essential Tools& Techniques

LinkedIn Learning

- Fundamentals of Digital Marketing
 Google Digital Garage
- Student Council Member
 Kingston University UK
- Non related references will be shared upon request.

I do hereby certify that the above particulars given by me are true and correct to the best of my knowledge. If I am offered an opportunity to serve in your esteemed company, I can assure you that I shall always perform duties with commitment & loyalty.

Sflur gudet